sundirect.in 2016-03-09

# Sun Direct DTH - Privacy Policy

Sun Direct takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. Registration Data and certain other information about you are subject to our Privacy Policy. In particular, We believe it is important for You to know how We treat information about You that We may receive from this Web site "www.sundirect.in" ("Site").In general, You can visit this site without telling Us who You are or revealing any information about Yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of the visitors. Computer, which connects it to the internet, and not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. Domain name information that we collect is not used to personally identify you and instead is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc.,

We use this information to measure the use of our site and to improve its content. In addition, there are portions of this Web site where We may need to collect personal information from You for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with certain information You request. The information collected from You may include Your name, address, telephone, fax number, or e-mail address, etc. This Privacy Policy is applicable to any personal information, which is given by You to Us ("User Information") via this Site and is devised to help You feel more confident about the privacy and security of Your personal details. When You leave your contact details please note that We are not bound to reply. This Web site is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children, and we do not knowingly market our products or services to children.

##### **Data Collection**

When using the Site you may be asked to enter User Information. Such User Information will only be used for the purposes for which it was collected, for any other purposes specified at the collection point and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

##### **How we may use Your data**

By entering Your User Information, You accept that We may retain Your User Information and that it may be held by Us or any third party company which processes it on Our behalf. Sun Direct does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies.

##### **We shall be entitled to Use Your User Information for the following purposes:**

  * Market research, including statistical analysis of User behavior which We may disclose to third parties in depersonalized, aggregated form.
  * In order to enable Us to comply with any requirements imposed on Us by law.
  * In order to send You periodic communications (this may include e-mail), about features, products and services, events and special offers. Such communications from Us may include advertising for third party companies or organizations.
  * For your convenience you can withdraw consent by replying to the "unsubscribe" link in e-mails from us.

Please also note that we do not disclose your personal information to third parties to enable them to send you direct marketing without Your permission to do so.

##### **Security of Data Collected**

We maintain strict physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. We restrict access to information about you to those Sun Direct employees who need to know the information to respond to your inquiry or request. Employees who misuse personal information are subject to disciplinary action.

##### **Contact Us**

If You have any questionsabout this privacy policy, please use the Contact Us page. We welcome Your questions and suggestions about Our privacy policy.

##### **Changes to this Policy**

Please check this privacy policy to inform Yourself of any change. Any site that You may connect to from here is not covered by this privacy policy.
